http://www.peterboroughdiocese.org/privacy

Close
Close
Browser Compatibility Notification
It appears you are trying to access this site using an outdated browser.
As a result, parts of the site may not function properly for you.
We recommend updating your browser to its most recent version at your earliest convenience.
Email
Privacy StatementParish AdministrationAccessibilityArchivesBishopClergyConnectDiocesan CommitteesDiocesan Pastoral CentreDiocesan Youth CommissionEmployment OpportunitiesFinancial Reports of the DioceseGeography of the DioceseHistory of the DioceseMagazineNewsParishesPastoral PlanningPoliciesResponsible MinistryTruth and ReconciliationVatican Website
Subscribe to this page
Terms of Use
The information on the Roman Catholic Episcopal Corporation for the Diocese of Peterborough ("the Diocese") internet site at www.peterboroughdiocese.org is updated regularly and considered current and accurate. The Diocese reserves the right to discontinue, change or modify this site at any time without notice.
Links or references to other websites, organizations, products, services or publications do not imply endorsement or approval by the Diocese. By using this website you are agreeing to be bound by the Terms of Use.
Privacy Statement
Protecting your privacy and your personal data is important to the Diocese of Peterborough. The Diocese is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. Any personal data relating to you will only be used and recorded by us in accordance with current data protection legislation and this Privacy Policy.
Most of the information accessible on the Diocese's website does not require you to identify yourself at all. You may access it anonymously. However, the Diocese does collection personal information about you when you choose to provide it. We endeavor to collect only as much personal information as is necessary to assist you in conducting your business with the Diocese.
We collect and retain personal information for the following purposes:
To process your requests for services or further information;
To communicate with you regarding services or information that you have requested or received;
To identify you if you have a query or concern about the service that you requested or received;
To meet legal and regulatory requirements.
Compliance
Our practices have been designed to ensure compliance with the privacy provisions of the Municipal Freedom of Information and Protection of Privacy Act [Ontario]. The Diocese endeavors to make its information as accessible as possible to the public; however some records contain information that is either confidential or personal in nature.
Use and Disclosure of Information
The Diocese is the sole owner of the information collected on its site. We will not sell, share, rent or otherwise disclose your personal information to any organization or individual outside the Diocese.
The Diocese's web server logs visitor activity to help manage the website. Information stored in logs does not identify visitors personally. The logs store the IP address from which the site was accessed; the type of operating system used; and the date and time the site was accessed.
External Links
The Diocese's site has links to other sites that may collect personally identifiable information about visitors. This privacy policy does not cover third party data collection practices and the Diocese of Peterborough does not assume any responsibilities for the actions of third parties.
Contact Us
×
